Manschinger, Kurt and Grete Hartwig; Papers ger025
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Artistic Works, 1916-1984; 3; 10.94 cubic ft.
  - Children: The Singing and Springing Little Lark Based on a German Fairy Tale, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Choral Vocal: Bebel Festspiel, 1933; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Common Place Book (Scrap Book Greta Hartwig), 1917; 1921-1922; 1924-1929 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Concerts: A Concert of Music by Ashley Vernon, Carnegie Recital Hall (1 of 2), 1974 April 27 (Reel 7)
  - Concerts: A Concert of Music by Ashley Vernon, Carnegie Recital Hall (2 of 2), 1974 April 27 (Reel 8)
  - Concerts: National Association For American Composers and Conductors, 1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cubiculo Also Maurice Edwards, 1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Daily Vocal Exercises, Greta Hartwig Manschinger, 1967 (Lp 1)
    General
    Multiple copies
  - Dance Play: Adolescence - A Ballet Scenario, and Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dance Play: Is This Trip Necessary 1st Version, 2nd Version and Programs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dance Playlet: The Organ - Grinder's Little Helper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Denise, Musical Recordings, Undated (Reel 48)
  - Die Flotte Von Toulon, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Der Freidenker/The Freethinker, Including Articles About Theodor Hartwig, 1947; 1952; 1962 (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
  - Der Tinten Fisch, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Die Seechlange" Programs, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Drafts of Articles for Music Magazines on Vernon/Manschinger, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - E.B. Marks and Kurt Manschinger's Other Copy Work on Montezuma by Roger Session, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Emceeing, 1951-1952; 1962; 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Esther, Musical Recordings, Undated (Reel 46)
  - Ferdinand Raimund-Feier, Undated (Reel 31)
  - "Flashback to Vienna in the Late 20's", 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - German Translations of America Expressions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Greta Hartwig, Art, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Greta Hartwig, Complete, Part 1, Undated (Reel 32)
  - Greta Hartwig, Complete, Part 2, Undated (Reel 33)
  - Greta Hartwig, Complete, Part 3, Undated (Reel 34)
  - Greta Hartwig, Complete, Part 4, Undated (Reel 35)
  - Greta Hartwig, Drawing and Sketches, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Greta Hartwig, Fragments and Unfinished Scenes, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Greta Hartwig, French Poems, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Greta Hartwig, Lyrics-Miscellaneous: Original Lyrics By Others, 1943-1944; 1947; 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Greta Hartwig, Miscellaneous Song Translations and Introductions, 1979; 1933; 1941; 1945-1948; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Greta Hartwig, Newspaper Clips English, 1955-1958; 1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Greta Hartwig, Poetry and Novel Submissions, 1969; 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Greta Hartwig, Publicity: Literary Works, 1946-1949; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Greta Hartwig, Publicity: Newspaper Clips, German, 1943; 1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Greta Hartwig, Publicity: Reviews (English), 1947; 1955; 1963 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Greta Hartwig, Songs and Readings with Piano, Undated (Reel 23)
  - Greta Hartwig, Special Material, 1948; 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Greta Hartwig, Special Material (Original), 1948-1950; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Greta Hartwig, Translation - German Version of American Folk Songs, 1947; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Greta Hartwig, Works - German, English, M.C., 1945-1969 (Card-file 1)
  - Greta Hartwig, Writing Fragments, 1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Greta Hartwig, Writing: New Yorker Bilderbagen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Greta Hartwig's Poems for German Commercial Advertising, 1935-1938; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Greta Hartwig's Suggestions and Ideas for Literary Works - German, 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Greta's Words and Translations - Music By Others, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
  - Gold and Tinsel: A Poetic Farrago, 1959 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - The Harry Wolf Show, W.S. Broms Interview, KSTP-AM/FM, 1976 February 1 (Reel 42)
  - Hartwig - Manschinger: Programs, Brochures, Catalogues, Etc., 1939; 1961-1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Haydn: The Apothecary, 1956 July 26 (Reel 38)
  - Heine Lieder - Bea and Carroll, Kurt Manschinger and Greta Hartwig, 1958; 1963; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Herbert Haufrecht, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Herz, Das Die Freiheit Liebt, 1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Hotshki, Votski - Words and Music By Greta Hartwig, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
  - I Dreamed Again, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - "Ich Meine Dasselbe" (Ein Lehrscherz), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Illustration, Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Immer Singen (Trio), Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Instrumental: "Elf Chansons", Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Instrumental: "Quintet", 1953; 1969; Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - The Interrupted Symphony, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
  - The Interrupted Symphony, Undated (Reel 20)
  - The Interrupted Symphony, Piano and Orchestra Versions, Undated (Reel 37)
  - Intros, 1957; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Ismell Lilles (Duet), 1938; Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
  - Jan (Popper), Musical Recordings, Undated (Reel 47)
  - John Wilson, 1969; 1972-1978; Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Kennen Sie Den, 1940 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Kinderlied (30 Songs, No. 22), 1932 (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
  - "King David" and "Warning" by Heinrich Heine, Tr. By Mimi Grossberg, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kleinkunst in America (WBOS) and Triumph of Punch Review (WBAI), 1969; Undated (Reel 26)
  - Kleinkunstlieder von Kurt Manschinger, Undated (Reel 37)
  - Kleinkunstlieder, Radio WCAM, Philadelphia (1 of 2), Undated (Reel 38)
  - Kleinkunstlieder, Radio WCAM, Philadelphia (2 of 2), Undated (Reel 40)
  - Korbereretten, Undated (Reel 24)
  - Kurt Manschinger, Articles, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Kurt Manschinger, Choral and Folk Song Arrangements (Not Original Works), Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
  - Kurt Manschinger, Programs: The Lantern London, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kurt Manschinger, "Recollections of Anton Von Webern", Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kurt Manschinger, "Say, A Strange Thing Happened to Me", 1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kurt Manschinger, Song Arr.: Choral, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Laughter and Tears from Shakespeare (Reel 18)
  - Lecture - Recital: Chekov, 1953; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lecture - Recital: Deutsche Lyrik Von Goethe bis Heute, 1958 November 22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lecture - Recital: Goethe, 1965 June 5 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lecture - Recital: Heine, 1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lecture - Recital: Viennese Miniature Song/ The Little Art Song, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lecture - Recitals: Nestray Talisman and F. Raimund (See Also One Woman Shows), 1931; 1957-1963; 1966-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Libretto: April in Vienna, English, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Libretto: A Bagetelle, 1957; 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Libretto: Behold The Wandering Moon, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Libretto: Blue Bell, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Libretto: Eternally Yours, English, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Libretto: The God and The Bayadere (From Goethe), English, 1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Libretto: The Herebefore, 1949; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Libretto: In the Factory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Libretto (Manschinger): Der Talisman, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Libretto (Manschinger): Der Talisman, Undated (Reel 30)
  - Libretto (Manschinger): Der Talisman, WCAM Radio Broadcast and Excerpts of Greta Hartwig's Recitation, Undated (Reel 19)
  - Libretto: (Manschinger): Ferdinand Raimund Reier, 1962; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Libretto: Temptations, English, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Libretto: The Red and The Black, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Libretto: Tragic Triangle, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Libretto (Translated): Haydn: The Apothecary, 1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Libretto (Translated): Cimarosa: The Secret Marriage and Notes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Libretto (Translated): Gluck: Don Juan, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Libretto (Translated): Mozart: Bastien and Bastienne, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Lied Des Ein Fachen Menschen, 1939; 1946; Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 9)
  - Lied des Kuli, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Lu Hsing, 1942; 1945-1947; 1953; 1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Lu Hsing (1 of 2), 1947; 1955; 1957 (Reel 9)
  - Lu Hsing (2 of 2), 1947; 1955; 1957 (Reel 10)
  - Lyrics: Assorted Lyrics A Through L, 1944-1956; 1960-1964; 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Lyrics: Assorted Lyrics M Through Z, 1949-1950; 1954; 1959-1960; 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Lyrics: Ein Ton, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Lyrics: Sword and Flower: A Collection of Lyrics From The Repertoire of Greta Hartwig, 1932; 1943; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lyrics: Translation Berloiz: Wilbur Broms Re: Moore Book, 1961; 1963; 1964; 1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Lyrics: Translation Miscellaneous Songs, 1948; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Mela Hartwig, "Die andere Wirklichkeit," in Literature and Criticism and a Memorial to Hartwig, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Mela Hartwig, Art, Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mela Hartwig, "Das Weib Ist Ein Nichts", Synopsis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mela Hartwig, "Georgslegende," in German Review/Deutsche Rundschou, 1960 August (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Mela Hartwig, "Miracle of Ulm", Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Many Happy Returns, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 1)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Flowers in Vase with Glass on Tabletop, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 7)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Mountain and Water, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 9)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Mountain Scene with Church, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Mountain Scene with House, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Pink Flowers, Undated (Map-tube 1)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Pink and Red Flowers, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 10)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Purple Flowers in Glass Bowl, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Red Edged Flowers, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 8)
  - Mela Hartwig, Painting, Untitled, Village Scene, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 2)
  - Mela Hartwig, Pastel Drawing, Untitled, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 3)
  - Mela Hartwig, Poetry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mela Hartwig, Photographs of Art, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mela Hartwig, Programs and Reviews, 1956; 1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mercedes Lois, 1980; Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Mice in Council, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Micky-Maus Lernt Singen (Der Imiboquo-Mibubribrg No. 7) (30 Songs, No. 14), Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 10)
  - Mille Fleurs, Inspiration, 1947-1948; Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mille Fleurs, Programs and Reviews, 1958; Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Music Note Book - Music and Poems and Translations by Greta Hartwig, Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Musical Comedy Class, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Nachdich Tungen Nach Verlaine Von Mela Hartwig, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Natalie Costa, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - National Association For American Composer and Conductors Concert of February 12, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Non, Je n'irae Plus au bois, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Norman Siegel Songs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Novel: Brno- New York Biographical-Unfinished (English), 1946-1948; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Novel: Didi Faehrt Nach Amerika- German - English (1 of 2), 1947-1948; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Novel: Didi Faehrt Nach Amerika- German - English (2 of 2), 1947-1948; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Novel: Die Todesaugen (The Demon) With Paul Fredricksen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Novel: Five Leaf Clover (1 of 2), 1946-1947; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Novel: Five Leaf Clover (2 of 2), 1946-1947; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Novel: Gingerette (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Novel: Gingerette (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Novel: I Must Not Disturb My Husband - English (1 of 3), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Novel: I Must Not Disturb My Husband - English (2 of 3), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Novel: I Must Not Disturb My Husband - English (3 of 3), 1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Novel: Mamas Lebensbeichte, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Novel: Rendezvous In Manhattan Sketches - Publication, 1947-1950; 1954; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Novel: Tracollo, The Thief, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Novel: Weekend Mit Monika (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Novel: Weekend Mit Monika (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Nuv Ein Moment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - One Woman Shows, 1961; 1963-1967; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - One-Woman Shows: Assorted Performances (1 of 2), 1950; 1954; 1963-1964; 1969; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - One-Woman Shows: Assorted Performances (2 of 2), 1950; 1954; 1963-1964; 1969; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - One-Woman Shows: Austrian Inst., 1964; 1967-1968; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - One-Woman Shows: Literary Tea "Sie Suchen Sine Koechin", Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - One-Woman Shows: Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - One-Woman Shows: Rehearsal, Part 1, 1963 (Reel 21)
  - One-Woman Shows: Rehearsal, Part 2, 1963 (Reel 22)
  - Opera: The Apothecary, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, 1948; 1953; 1969; 1976; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Orchestra Score, 1948 (Oversize 6)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Beginning, 1976 August 2 (Reel 43)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Complete (1 of 3), 1976 August 2 (Reel 45)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Complete (2 of 3), 1976 August 2 (Reel 50)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Complete (3 of 3), 1976 August 2 (Reel 56)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Complete, 1976 August 2 (Cassette 1)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Conclusion, 1976 August 2 (Reel 44)
  - Opera: The Barber of New York, Excerpts from Carnegie Recital Hall, 1974 April 27 (Reel 56)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, 1950; 1956-1957; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, 1956 (Oversize 3, Folder 11)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, Undated (Reel 39)
    Scene 3 incomplete.
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, Love Scene, Undated (Oversize 6)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, The Turnau Opera Players, Voice of America Broadcast (1 of 3), 1956 July 29 (Reel 27)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, The Turnau Opera Players, Voice of America Broadcast (2 of 3), 1956 July 29 (Reel 28)
  - Opera: Cupid and Psyche, The Turnau Opera Players, Voice of America Broadcast (3 of 3), 1956 July 29 (Reel 29)
  - Opera: Grand Slam, 1955-1959; 1970; 1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Opera: Grand Slam, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 12)
  - Opera: Grand Slam, The Turnau Opera Players (1 of 3), 1955 (Reel 1)
  - Opera: Grand Slam, The Turnau Opera Players (2 of 3), 1955 (Reel 2)
  - Opera: Grand Slam, The Turnau Opera Players (3 of 3), 1955 (Reel 36)
  - Opera: Hansel and Gretel, 1956-1957; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Opera: Hansel and Gretel, Undated (Reel 25)
  - Opera: A Husband at The Door (1 of 2), 1959-1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Opera: A Husband at The Door (2 of 2), 1959-1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Opera: A Husband at The Door, Undated (Reel 39)
    Unrehearsed performance.
  - Opera: Madame Dorette, 1947; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Opera: Triumph of Punch, 1941; 1968-1971; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Opera: Triumph of Punch, Orchestra Score, 1954 (Oversize 7)
  - Opera: Triumph of Punch, Overture, Score, Undated (Oversize 7)
  - Opera: Triumph of Punch, The New Haven Opera Society, 1971 (Reel 4)
    Poor sound and background noise. Opera heavily cut.
  - Opera Workshop Productions: Manschingers and Irene Paulson (1956) - Other Programs, 1956-1957; 1960; 1964; 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Orchestral: Mille Fleurs, NAACC Festival Orchestra at the Festival of American Music at Carnegie Hall (1 of 2), 1958 (Reel 5)
  - Orchestral: Mille Fleurs, NAACC Festival Orchestra at the Festival of American Music at Carnegie Hall (2 of 2), 1958 (Reel 6)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, Score, 1965 (Oversize 7)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, Score with Annotations, 1965 (Oversize 7)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, The Orchestra of America, Town Hall Broadcast, 1966 (Reel 49)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, The Orchestra of America at the Town Hall American Music Festival and The Ohio University Symphony Orchestra at the Premiere Performance (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Reel 5)
  - Orchestral: Sinfonietta, The Orchestra of America at the Town Hall American Music Festival and The Ohio University Symphony Orchestra at the Premiere Performance (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Reel 6)
  - Orchestral: Symphony in Two Movements, Score, Undated (Oversize 7)
  - Original Poetry and Lyrics By Greta Hartwig, 1944-1971; Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Otto Jaki Songs, 1947; 1952; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Partition of The Earth By Schiller Translated by Greta Hartwig, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Photographs and Resumes of Students of Greta Hartwig, 1956; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Plays: The Dark Voice, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Plays: House Wives, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Playlet: The Fanastic Concert, 1945; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Poetry by Greta's Mother "Kathe", 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Poetry by Others, 1947-1948; 1951-1952; 1959; 1970; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Poster About the Saratoga Spa Festival Featuring Ashley Vernon, ca. 1947 (Oversize 6)
  - Poster for Bagatelle, Undated (Oversize 8, Folder 11)
  - Poster for "Books of Life" Featuring Die Tragdie des Schlafzimmers, Written by Theodor Hartwig, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - Program and Materials for Greta Hartwig Manschinger Memorial Concert (May 23, 1971), Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Program and Materials for Kurt Manschinger Concert (April 27, 1974), 1972; 1974-1975; Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Program and Materials for Manschinger Commemorative Concert (April 15, 1972), 1971-1972; Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Program and Materials for Memorial Concert For Kurt Manschinger, (February 23, 1969), Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Program for Greta Hartwig Manschinger Memorial Concert (May 23, 1971) (1 of 2), 1971 May 23 (Reel 3)
  - Program for Greta Hartwig Manschinger Memorial Concert (May 23, 1971) (2 of 2), 1971 May 23 (Reel 41)
  - Program for Memorial Concert for Kurt Manschinger (February 23, 1971), 1971 February 23 (Reel 24)
    Does not include last three songs.
  - Program for Memorial Concert for Kurt Manschinger (February 23, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Programs: Flier Masters, 1947-1948; 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Programs: Greta's Showcases, Etc., 1952-1953; 1970-1971; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Programs: Greta Hartwig as Stage Director, 1952-1953; 1956; 1968; Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Programs: Kiein Kunst-Lieder, 1939; 1941-1946; 1963; Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Programs: Laughter and Tears From Shakespeare, 1969; Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Programs: Lecture and Lecture - Recital by Greta Hartwig, 1947-1948; 1957-1960; 1968; Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Programs: Little Harlequinade, 1952; 1956-1957; 1963; 1967; Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Programs: One-Women Shows, 1942; 1970; Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Programs: School (NYCOM, Mannes, Mahatten, Juilliard, etc.) Where Greta Hartwig Taught or Where Her Work was Performed, 1951-1954; 1956; 1970; Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Programs: Turnau, 1954-1957; 1964; 1972-1973; 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Programs: Variety (With Other Performers and Assisting Artists), 1940; 1968-1969; Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Programs and Reviews, Former Students, 1954-1956; 1959-1960; 1963-1970; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Programs and Reviews Saratoga Spa Music Festival, 1947; 1952; 1976-1977; Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Prologue - "I'm So Happy You Could be Here", 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Published Stories By Greta Hartwig (In German), 1929; 1937; 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Quintet, Carnegie Recital Hall, 1974 April 27 (Reel 56)
    Cut version.
  - Quintet, First Performance, Complete, Undated (Reel 56)
  - Quintet for Violin, Clarinet, Horn, Bassoon and Piano, Abbreviated, Greenwood Productions, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1976 February 8 (Reel 45)
  - Quintet for Violin, Clarinet, Horn, Bassoon and Piano, Greenwood Productions, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1976 February 8 (Reel 43)
  - Quintet for Violin, Clarinet, Horn, Cello and Piano, Undated (Reel 11)
  - Quo Vadis (Der Imiboquo-Mibubriobro, No. 9) (30 Songs, No. 13), Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 13)
  - Radio: "Rettung Durch Paganini", 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Radio: "Wein, was Falltdenn Dir nur ein?" ("Vienna What do You Think of?"), 1963 January 27 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Radio and TV: Carol, Gegory and A Piano, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Radio and TV: Commercial Jingles, 1949; 1950; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Radio and TV: "Everybody Tries" Script, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Remember, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rhapsody for Oboe and Orchestra, Piano and Orchestra Versions, 1947; 1969 (Reel 11)
  - Saint Peter's Gate Program, Rehearsal, 1970 (Reel 23)
  - Sheet Music: And Mona Lisa Smile, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sheet Music: Angsttraum (30 Songs, No. 21), 1932 (Oversize 3, Folder 14)
  - Sheet Music: Arme Maquise!, 1936 (Oversize 3, Folder 15)
  - Sheet Music: Barb'ra Allen, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 16)
  - Sheet Music: Bauernmaochen in der Sttrassenbahn (30 Songs, No. 20), 1932 (Oversize 3, Folder 17)
  - Sheet Music: Bilde Einen Reinen Einfachen Satz, 1936 February (Oversize 3, Folder 18)
  - Sheet Music: Bill Bailey for Three Women's Voices and Piano, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 19)
  - Sheet Music: Black is the Color of My True Love's Hair (American Song), Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 20)
  - Sheet Music: Bluhende Garten, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 21)
  - Sheet Music: Bumerang (Der Imiboquo-Mibubribro, No. 5) (30 Songs, No. 15), Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 22)
  - Sheet Music: Can-Can ("Gossip") For Three Women's Voices and Piano, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 23)
  - Sheet Music: Chinese Dance, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sheet Music: Clarissa Sagt Telefonisch, 1963 December 12 (Oversize 3, Folder 24)
  - Sheet Music: Clair De Lune for Three Women's Voices and Piano, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 25)
  - Sheet Music: Cockles and Mussels, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 26)
  - Sheet Music: Daily Vocal Exercises by Greta Hartwig Manschinger, Undated (Oversize 3, Folder 27)
  - Sheet Music: Das Broselein (Der Imiboquo-Mibribro No.8) (30 Songs, No. 28), Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music: Das Deutesche Lied De Freiheit, 1942 June 8 (Oversize 4, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Music: Denn Su Lang, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sheet Music: Der Athlet, 1934 (Oversize 4, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music: Der Brief Mark (Der Imiboquo-Mibubribro, No. 4) (30 Songs, No.27), Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Music: Der Flieger (30 Songs, No. 7), 1931 (Oversize 4, Folder 5)
  - Sheet Music: Der Imiboquo-Mibubribro (See Also Individual Songs and See Also 30 Songs), Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 6)
  - Sheet Music: Die Ballafe Vom Hustenden Frosch (30 Songs, No. 16), 1932 (Oversize 4, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music: Die Mittagzeitung (Der Imiboquo-Mibubribro, No. 3) (30 Songs, No. 1), Undated (Oversize 4, Folder 8)
  - Sheet Music: Die Verstanden Frau, 1937 February (Oversize 4, Folder 9)